articlesnow4u.com 2018-12-18

# Privacy Policy

Articlesnow4u.com (" **Articlesnow4u** ") operates Articlesnow4u.com and may operate other websites. It is Articlesnow4u's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

**Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, Articlesnow4u collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Articlesnow4u's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Articlesnow4u's visitors use its website. From time to time, Articlesnow4u may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Articlesnow4u also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on Articlesnow4u.com blogs/sites. Articlesnow4u only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to Articlesnow4u's websites choose to interact with Articlesnow4u in ways that require Articlesnow4u to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Articlesnow4u gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at Articlesnow4u.com to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Articlesnow4u are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Articlesnow4u collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Articlesnow4u. Articlesnow4u does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Aggregated Statistics**

Articlesnow4u may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Articlesnow4u may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Articlesnow4u does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**

Articlesnow4u discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Articlesnow4u's behalf or to provide services available at Articlesnow4u's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Articlesnow4u's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Articlesnow4u will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Articlesnow4u discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Articlesnow4u believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Articlesnow4u, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Articlesnow4u website and have supplied your email address, Articlesnow4u may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Articlesnow4u and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Articlesnow4u takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Articlesnow4u uses cookies to help Articlesnow4u identify and track visitors, their usage of Articlesnow4u website, and their website access preferences. Articlesnow4u visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Articlesnow4u's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Articlesnow4u's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Business Transfers**

If Articlesnow4u, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Articlesnow4u goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Articlesnow4u may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

**Ads**

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Articlesnow4u and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Articlesnow4u may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Articlesnow4u's sole discretion. Articlesnow4u encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a Articlesnow4u.com account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
